With a simple wound, we can go from this step, on to the vet wrap, with a similar idea.
I like to start somewhat in the middle, to secure that gauze in place, putting a little bit of pressure over the wound.
Then, I'll go up, making sure I go high enough to hopefully secure it, without it being able to slip down.
That wrap of course, is a handy item, something that we ought to have, real close by.
We don't want to pull it so tight, that we create any circulatory compromise, but we definitely want to wrap and wrap, and use as much of it, as we think necessary, to keep this wrap from slipping down.
This is the kind of a wrap that we could use on just about any extremity, so long as we recognize, that if we put this wrap in place, we've got to be able to get our fingers underneath, at the top and the bottom, but keeping it secure enough, so that it's not going to slip.
And as I continue this around, you can also, if for any reason you thought you can apply a little tape to the end, duct tape or something, that will help keep this.
But this usually sticks very well to itself, and there's never much trouble in keeping that together.
I'd say that wrap should stay pretty well in place.
I can still tell if that should soak through, and if it were saturated, I'd know I would need to replace that.